Evil Lies Within
The Canal is a horror, mystery, thriller film directed by Ivan Kavanagh.
A man who suspects his wife is cheating on him begins having nightmarish
visions of an evil presence that he believes inhabits his house.
David, played by Rupert Evans.
Claire, played by Antonia Campbell-Hughes.
Alice, played by Hannah Hoekstra.
McNamara, played by Steve Oram.
Sophie, played by Kelly Byrne.
Estate Agent, played by Serena Brabazon.
The Canal is a 2014 Irish horror film that was
directed and written by Ivan Kavanagh.
The film had its world premiere on 18 April 2014, at the Tribeca Film Festival, and stars Rupert Evans as
a father investigating a horrific murder that took place in his home in the early 1900s.
The film explores themes of husband wife relationship,
cheating, pregnancy, supernatural, haunted.
The tone is intense and dark and mind_bending.